<rss version="2.0"><channel>
  <item>
    <title>Lawmakers debate transport funding extension as talks continue</title>
    <link>https://example.com/ap-top-news/story-1</link>
    <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 23:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    <description>Lawmakers debate transport funding extension as talks continue with additional context and follow-up details for the daily brief.</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>State health agency publishes new winter safety advisory</title>
    <link>https://example.com/ap-top-news/story-2</link>
    <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 22:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    <description>State health agency publishes new winter safety advisory with additional context and follow-up details for the daily brief.</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>School districts announce updates to remote learning plans</title>
    <link>https://example.com/ap-top-news/story-3</link>
    <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 21:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    <description>School districts announce updates to remote learning plans with additional context and follow-up details for the daily brief.</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>City councils approve housing incentive pilot programs</title>
    <link>https://example.com/ap-top-news/story-4</link>
    <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 20:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    <description>City councils approve housing incentive pilot programs with additional context and follow-up details for the daily brief.</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Farmers report mixed yields after dry summer months</title>
    <link>https://example.com/ap-top-news/story-5</link>
    <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 19:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    <description>Farmers report mixed yields after dry summer months with additional context and follow-up details for the daily brief.</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Coast guard responds to severe storm damage along shoreline</title>
    <link>https://example.com/ap-top-news/story-6</link>
    <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 18:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    <description>Coast guard responds to severe storm damage along shoreline with additional context and follow-up details for the daily brief.</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Judges hear arguments in high-profile voting rights case</title>
    <link>https://example.com/ap-top-news/story-7</link>
    <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    <description>Judges hear arguments in high-profile voting rights case with additional context and follow-up details for the daily brief.</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Officials expand grants for small business recovery</title>
    <link>https://example.com/ap-top-news/story-8</link>
    <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    <description>Officials expand grants for small business recovery with additional context and follow-up details for the daily brief.</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Police departments launch regional data-sharing initiative</title>
    <link>https://example.com/ap-top-news/story-9</link>
    <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    <description>Police departments launch regional data-sharing initiative with additional context and follow-up details for the daily brief.</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Utility regulators examine surge pricing complaints</title>
    <link>https://example.com/ap-top-news/story-10</link>
    <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    <description>Utility regulators examine surge pricing complaints with additional context and follow-up details for the daily brief.</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Water authorities issue conservation guidance ahead of heatwave</title>
    <link>https://example.com/ap-top-news/story-11</link>
    <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    <description>Water authorities issue conservation guidance ahead of heatwave with additional context and follow-up details for the daily brief.</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Senate committee advances ethics transparency package</title>
    <link>https://example.com/ap-top-news/story-12</link>
    <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    <description>Senate committee advances ethics transparency package with additional context and follow-up details for the daily brief.</description>
  </item>
</channel></rss>