<rss version="2.0"><channel>
  <item>
    <title>Trade ministers schedule emergency consultation on tariff tensions</title>
    <link>https://example.com/bbc-world/story-1</link>
    <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 23:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    <description>Trade ministers schedule emergency consultation on tariff tensions with additional context and follow-up details for the daily brief.</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Arctic research mission reports accelerated sea-ice movement</title>
    <link>https://example.com/bbc-world/story-2</link>
    <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 22:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    <description>Arctic research mission reports accelerated sea-ice movement with additional context and follow-up details for the daily brief.</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>European leaders discuss coordinated migration framework</title>
    <link>https://example.com/bbc-world/story-3</link>
    <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 21:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    <description>European leaders discuss coordinated migration framework with additional context and follow-up details for the daily brief.</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Rail workers vote on updated national pay proposal</title>
    <link>https://example.com/bbc-world/story-4</link>
    <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 20:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    <description>Rail workers vote on updated national pay proposal with additional context and follow-up details for the daily brief.</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Scientists publish findings on coral recovery hotspots</title>
    <link>https://example.com/bbc-world/story-5</link>
    <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 19:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    <description>Scientists publish findings on coral recovery hotspots with additional context and follow-up details for the daily brief.</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Aid convoys reach isolated communities after flooding</title>
    <link>https://example.com/bbc-world/story-6</link>
    <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 18:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    <description>Aid convoys reach isolated communities after flooding with additional context and follow-up details for the daily brief.</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Tech regulators review AI safety disclosure commitments</title>
    <link>https://example.com/bbc-world/story-7</link>
    <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    <description>Tech regulators review AI safety disclosure commitments with additional context and follow-up details for the daily brief.</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Currency volatility prompts central bank intervention talk</title>
    <link>https://example.com/bbc-world/story-8</link>
    <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    <description>Currency volatility prompts central bank intervention talk with additional context and follow-up details for the daily brief.</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>New archaeological discovery opens debate on conservation access</title>
    <link>https://example.com/bbc-world/story-9</link>
    <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    <description>New archaeological discovery opens debate on conservation access with additional context and follow-up details for the daily brief.</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Public broadcaster expands election fact-check unit</title>
    <link>https://example.com/bbc-world/story-10</link>
    <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    <description>Public broadcaster expands election fact-check unit with additional context and follow-up details for the daily brief.</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Hospital network pilots new wait-time triage model</title>
    <link>https://example.com/bbc-world/story-11</link>
    <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    <description>Hospital network pilots new wait-time triage model with additional context and follow-up details for the daily brief.</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Cybersecurity teams investigate major service outage</title>
    <link>https://example.com/bbc-world/story-12</link>
    <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    <description>Cybersecurity teams investigate major service outage with additional context and follow-up details for the daily brief.</description>
  </item>
</channel></rss>
