<rss version="2.0"><channel>
  <item>
    <title>EU ministers seek breakthrough on asylum reform package</title>
    <link>https://example.com/guardian-world/story-1</link>
    <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 23:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    <description>EU ministers seek breakthrough on asylum reform package with additional context and follow-up details for the daily brief.</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Researchers warn of accelerating glacier retreat in alpine regions</title>
    <link>https://example.com/guardian-world/story-2</link>
    <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 22:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    <description>Researchers warn of accelerating glacier retreat in alpine regions with additional context and follow-up details for the daily brief.</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Rights groups call for safeguards in protest policing reforms</title>
    <link>https://example.com/guardian-world/story-3</link>
    <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 21:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    <description>Rights groups call for safeguards in protest policing reforms with additional context and follow-up details for the daily brief.</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Cities test fare-free transport weekends to cut emissions</title>
    <link>https://example.com/guardian-world/story-4</link>
    <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 20:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    <description>Cities test fare-free transport weekends to cut emissions with additional context and follow-up details for the daily brief.</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Court reviews legality of expanded surveillance contracts</title>
    <link>https://example.com/guardian-world/story-5</link>
    <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 19:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    <description>Court reviews legality of expanded surveillance contracts with additional context and follow-up details for the daily brief.</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Aid organizations report gaps in refugee housing capacity</title>
    <link>https://example.com/guardian-world/story-6</link>
    <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 18:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    <description>Aid organizations report gaps in refugee housing capacity with additional context and follow-up details for the daily brief.</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Developers pledge new standards for carbon-neutral housing</title>
    <link>https://example.com/guardian-world/story-7</link>
    <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    <description>Developers pledge new standards for carbon-neutral housing with additional context and follow-up details for the daily brief.</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Consumer groups challenge telecom pricing increases</title>
    <link>https://example.com/guardian-world/story-8</link>
    <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    <description>Consumer groups challenge telecom pricing increases with additional context and follow-up details for the daily brief.</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Parliament debates long-term industrial strategy roadmap</title>
    <link>https://example.com/guardian-world/story-9</link>
    <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    <description>Parliament debates long-term industrial strategy roadmap with additional context and follow-up details for the daily brief.</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Hospitals pilot AI-assisted triage with human oversight</title>
    <link>https://example.com/guardian-world/story-10</link>
    <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    <description>Hospitals pilot AI-assisted triage with human oversight with additional context and follow-up details for the daily brief.</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Teachers unions push for nationwide workload framework</title>
    <link>https://example.com/guardian-world/story-11</link>
    <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    <description>Teachers unions push for nationwide workload framework with additional context and follow-up details for the daily brief.</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Water utilities accelerate upgrades after contamination alerts</title>
    <link>https://example.com/guardian-world/story-12</link>
    <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    <description>Water utilities accelerate upgrades after contamination alerts with additional context and follow-up details for the daily brief.</description>
  </item>
</channel></rss>