<rss version="2.0"><channel>
  <item>
    <title>Federal agencies release updated climate resilience guidance</title>
    <link>https://example.com/npr-news/story-1</link>
    <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 23:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    <description>Federal agencies release updated climate resilience guidance with additional context and follow-up details for the daily brief.</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>New poll finds voters split on healthcare expansion plan</title>
    <link>https://example.com/npr-news/story-2</link>
    <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 22:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    <description>New poll finds voters split on healthcare expansion plan with additional context and follow-up details for the daily brief.</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Researchers test battery recycling method for EV supply chains</title>
    <link>https://example.com/npr-news/story-3</link>
    <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 21:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    <description>Researchers test battery recycling method for EV supply chains with additional context and follow-up details for the daily brief.</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Transit advocates push for regional bus lane funding</title>
    <link>https://example.com/npr-news/story-4</link>
    <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 20:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    <description>Transit advocates push for regional bus lane funding with additional context and follow-up details for the daily brief.</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Community clinics prepare for expanded vaccination campaign</title>
    <link>https://example.com/npr-news/story-5</link>
    <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 19:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    <description>Community clinics prepare for expanded vaccination campaign with additional context and follow-up details for the daily brief.</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Judicial nominees face questions on digital rights precedent</title>
    <link>https://example.com/npr-news/story-6</link>
    <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 18:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    <description>Judicial nominees face questions on digital rights precedent with additional context and follow-up details for the daily brief.</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Public radio stations collaborate on election coverage project</title>
    <link>https://example.com/npr-news/story-7</link>
    <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    <description>Public radio stations collaborate on election coverage project with additional context and follow-up details for the daily brief.</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>State lawmakers weigh data privacy protections for teens</title>
    <link>https://example.com/npr-news/story-8</link>
    <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    <description>State lawmakers weigh data privacy protections for teens with additional context and follow-up details for the daily brief.</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Universities report increase in international applications</title>
    <link>https://example.com/npr-news/story-9</link>
    <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    <description>Universities report increase in international applications with additional context and follow-up details for the daily brief.</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Energy cooperatives invest in microgrid pilot deployments</title>
    <link>https://example.com/npr-news/story-10</link>
    <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    <description>Energy cooperatives invest in microgrid pilot deployments with additional context and follow-up details for the daily brief.</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Emergency responders train for severe weather season</title>
    <link>https://example.com/npr-news/story-11</link>
    <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    <description>Emergency responders train for severe weather season with additional context and follow-up details for the daily brief.</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Museums digitize archives for public access</title>
    <link>https://example.com/npr-news/story-12</link>
    <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    <description>Museums digitize archives for public access with additional context and follow-up details for the daily brief.</description>
  </item>
</channel></rss>