<rss version="2.0"><channel>
  <item>
    <title>Government reaches late budget compromise ahead of deadline</title>
    <link>https://example.com/reuters-world-news/story-1</link>
    <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 23:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    <description>Government reaches late budget compromise ahead of deadline with additional context and follow-up details for the daily brief.</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Central bank signals pause as inflation cools in major economies</title>
    <link>https://example.com/reuters-world-news/story-2</link>
    <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 22:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    <description>Central bank signals pause as inflation cools in major economies with additional context and follow-up details for the daily brief.</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Wildfire response expands after overnight wind shift</title>
    <link>https://example.com/reuters-world-news/story-3</link>
    <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 21:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    <description>Wildfire response expands after overnight wind shift with additional context and follow-up details for the daily brief.</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Global shipping group warns of longer transit disruptions</title>
    <link>https://example.com/reuters-world-news/story-4</link>
    <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 20:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    <description>Global shipping group warns of longer transit disruptions with additional context and follow-up details for the daily brief.</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Election commission confirms recount schedule in two regions</title>
    <link>https://example.com/reuters-world-news/story-5</link>
    <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 19:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    <description>Election commission confirms recount schedule in two regions with additional context and follow-up details for the daily brief.</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Energy ministers agree temporary supply coordination pact</title>
    <link>https://example.com/reuters-world-news/story-6</link>
    <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 18:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    <description>Energy ministers agree temporary supply coordination pact with additional context and follow-up details for the daily brief.</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Major airlines suspend selected routes after safety review</title>
    <link>https://example.com/reuters-world-news/story-7</link>
    <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    <description>Major airlines suspend selected routes after safety review with additional context and follow-up details for the daily brief.</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>UN aid agencies request emergency funding for drought response</title>
    <link>https://example.com/reuters-world-news/story-8</link>
    <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    <description>UN aid agencies request emergency funding for drought response with additional context and follow-up details for the daily brief.</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Court issues ruling on digital privacy enforcement scope</title>
    <link>https://example.com/reuters-world-news/story-9</link>
    <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    <description>Court issues ruling on digital privacy enforcement scope with additional context and follow-up details for the daily brief.</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Defense officials outline phased withdrawal timeline</title>
    <link>https://example.com/reuters-world-news/story-10</link>
    <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    <description>Defense officials outline phased withdrawal timeline with additional context and follow-up details for the daily brief.</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Public health agency tracks rise in seasonal admissions</title>
    <link>https://example.com/reuters-world-news/story-11</link>
    <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    <description>Public health agency tracks rise in seasonal admissions with additional context and follow-up details for the daily brief.</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Labor talks resume with transport union leaders</title>
    <link>https://example.com/reuters-world-news/story-12</link>
    <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    <description>Labor talks resume with transport union leaders with additional context and follow-up details for the daily brief.</description>
  </item>
</channel></rss>
